[
  {
    "question": "Who made this?",
    "answers": ["Flydiverny", "MrFluFFy", "Abakar", "God"],
    "correctAnswer": "MrFluFFy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Snus is probably made in...",
    "answers": ["Finland", "Norway", "Sweden", "Denmark"],
    "correctAnswer": "Sweden"
  },
  {
    "question": "Math is hard: 1+3",
    "answers": ["13", "31", "2", "4"],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is my brother?",
    "answers": ["Flydiverny", "MrFluFFy", "Abakar", "God"],
    "correctAnswer": "Flydiverny"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is my latest bought console?",
    "answers": ["PS5", "Switch", "Dreamcast", "Xbox360"],
    "correctAnswer": "Switch"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of my kids?",
    "answers": [
      "Freja and Sofie",
      "My and Jonas",
      "Leo and Fiona",
      "Gabriel and Jonathan"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Gabriel and Jonathan"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many cats?",
    "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "My cat names are based on?",
    "answers": ["Cars", "Game characters", "Gods", "Nothing"],
    "correctAnswer": "Gods"
  },
  {
    "question": "My cat names are based on?",
    "answers": ["Cars", "Game characters", "Gods", "Nothing"],
    "correctAnswer": "Gods"
  },
  {
    "question": "Highest rank reached in overwatch?",
    "answers": ["Master", "Gold", "Platinum", "Grand Master"],
    "correctAnswer": "Grand Master"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do i currently work?",
    "answers": ["Region Skåne", "Ikea", "Jayway", "Ica"],
    "correctAnswer": "Region Skåne"
  }
]
